Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Photographs
  - Subseries A: Production photographs
    - Dead End Kids photocopy, undated (Box 24, Folder 1018)
    - Dead End Kids press photos; "Devils in street", undated (Box 24, Folder 1019)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; print; Ellen McElduff & company, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1020)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; print, undated (Box 24, Folder 1021)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; prints; Ruth Maleczech as Marie Curie, undated (Box 24, Folder 1022)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; prints; Ellen McElduff, undated (Box 24, Folder 1023)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; print; "Hubba Hubba", undated (Box 24, Folder 1024)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; print; Terry O'Reilly, John Fistos, Michael Kuhling, Ellen McElduff, undated (Box 24, Folder 1025)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; prints; additional photos, undated (Box 24, Folder 1026)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; negatives, undated (Box 24, Folder 1027)
    - Dead End Kids Carol Rosegg; print; Ellen McElduff and David Brisbin, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1028)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Bob van Dantzig; prints, negatives; Amsterdam, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1029)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Bob van Dantzig; contact sheets; Amsterdam, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1030)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Richard Landry; contact sheets, negatives; April 12, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1031)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Richard Landry; prints, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1032)
    - Dressed Like an Egg Richard Landry; prints, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1033)
    - Epidog Julie Archer; print, undated (Box 25, Folder 1034)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Johan Elbers; prints, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1035)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; contact sheets, undated (Box 25, Folder 1036)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Fred & Greg shot I, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1037)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Black-Eyed Susan shot, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1038)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Pizza shot I, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1039)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Pizza shot II, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1040)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Fred & Greg shot II, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1041)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Greg Mehrten & Ann Shea shot, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1042)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; print; Felix & Black-Eyed Susan, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1043)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 1044)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg; prints, undated (Box 25, Folder 1045)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said Carol Rosegg, Johan Elbers; prints, photocopies; New York, undated (Box 25, Folder 1046)
    - 4 Stages Show Tina Girouard; prints; 112 Greene St; Jan, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 1047)
    - The Gospel at Colonus prints; Lee Breuer and Bob Telson, undated (Box 25, Folder 1048)
    - Hajj Georgina Bedrosian; color print; Ruth with mirror reflections and 3 video close-ups, undated (Box 25, Folder 1049)
    - Hajj Debra Richardson; prints, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1050)
    - Hajj Debra Richardson; print; Ruth with Lute on video; CalArts, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1051)
    - Hajj Georgina Bedrosian; prints; The Public Theater, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1052)
    - Hajj Nancy Campbell; print, undated (Box 25, Folder 1053)
    - Hajj Georgina Bedrosian, Donald Behrstock; prints, press, 1982-3 (Box 25, Folder 1054)
    - Help Wanted Nancy Campbell, Carol Rosegg; prints, undated (Box 25, Folder 1055)
    - Help Wanted Nancy Campbell, Carol Rosegg, Dona Ann McAdams; contact sheets, negatives, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1056)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine James Hamilton; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 1057)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine contact sheets, negatives; University of Iowa, [1986] (Box 25, Folder 1058)
    - In the Jungle of Cities James Hamilton; contact sheets, undated (Box 25, Folder 1059)
    - In the Jungle of Cities James Hamilton; prints; Ann Bogart, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1060)
    - In the Jungle of Cities color photocopies, undated (Box 25, Folder 1061)
    - It's a Man's World Robin Holland, Mitzi Trombo; prints, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1062)
    - It's a Man's World Thomas Consilvio, Mitzi Trombo; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 1063)
    - It's a Man's World Robin Holland; negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 1064)
    - Lear Michael Cooper; prints, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1065)
    - Lear Dona Ann McAdams; prints; Ruth as Lear, undated (Box 26, Folder 1066)
    - Lear Beatriz Schiller; prints; Triplex Theatre; Jan 9-Feb 11, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1067)
    - Lear print, undated (Box 26, Folder 1068)
    - Lear print; Toronto, undated (Box 26, Folder 1069)
    - Lear Michael Cooper; contact sheets; Toronto, undated (Box 26, Folder 1070)
    - Lear Paul Ryan; prints; rehearsal; Theatrical Outfit, Atlanta; Sept, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 1071)
    - Lear Robert Tobey; contact sheets, undated (Box 26, Folder 1072)
    - Lear Jonathan Atkin; prints; publicity shots, 1987-8 (Box 26, Folder 1073)
    - Lear Jonathan Atkin; prints; publicity shots; Winter, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1074)
    - Lear Jonathan Atkin; contact sheets, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1075)
    - The Lost Ones Richard Landry; print; David Warrilow's hand with figures, undated (Box 26, Folder 1076)
    - The Lost Ones Richard Landry; print; David Warrilow with figures, undated (Box 26, Folder 1077)
    - The Lost Ones Richard Landry; negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 1078)
    - The MahabharANTa prints, negatives; puppet workshop snapshots, undated (Box 26, Folder 1079)
    - The MahabharANTa Dona Ann McAdams; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 1080)
    - The MahabharANTa Dona Ann McAdams; prints, contact sheets; rehearsal, undated (Box 26, Folder 1081)
    - Mother Tom Brazil; contact sheets, undated (Box 26, Folder 1082)
    - Mother Dona Ann McAdams; print, negative; rehearsal, undated (Box 26, Folder 1083)
    - Mercier and Camier Bill Longcore; prints, color, undated (Box 26, Folder 1084)
    - Mercier and Camier Martha Swope; print, undated (Box 26, Folder 1085)
    - Play Tony Kent; print, contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 1086)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Amnon Ben Nomis; prints, flyer, undated (Box 26, Folder 1087)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice prints, undated (Box 26, Folder 1088)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Bob van Dantzig; prints, undated (Box 26, Folder 1089)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Carol Rosegg; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1090)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Terry O'Reilly; prints, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 1091)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various; negatives, contact sheets, undated (Box 27, Folder 1092)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice negatives, contact sheet; Steve Peabody, undated (Box 27, Folder 1093)
    - Pretty Boy Jerry Vezzuso; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1094)
    - Pretty Boy Jerry Vezzuso; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 1095)
    - Pretty Boy Georgina Bedrosian; print; publicity shot "Fistos looking at Drake", undated (Box 27, Folder 1096)
    - Pretty Boy Georgina Bedrosian; print; publicity shot "Fistos dancing with Drake", undated (Box 27, Folder 1097)
    - Pretty Boy Georgina Bedrosian; print; publicity shot "Mehrten grappled by Vawter", undated (Box 27, Folder 1098)
    - Pretty Boy Georgina Bedrosian; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1099)
    - Pretty Boy Georgina Bedrosian; negatives, contact sheets, undated (Box 27, Folder 1100)
    - Pretty Boy Nancy Campbell; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1101)
    - Pretty Boy Nancy Campbell; contact sheet, undated (Box 27, Folder 1102)
    - The Red Horse Animation Amnon Ben Nomis; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1103)
    - The Red Horse Animation Tom Berthiaume; print; Walker Art Center, undated (Box 27, Folder 1104)
    - The Red Horse Animation Peter Moore; print; rehearsal; Guggenheim, undated (Box 27, Folder 1105)
    - The Red Horse Animation Susan Mayer; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1106)
    - The Red Horse Animation Roberta Neiman; prints; Nova Scotia, undated (Box 27, Folder 1107)
    - The Red Horse Animation Roberta Neiman; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1108)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1109)
    - The Red Horse Animation Babette Mangolte; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1110)
    - The Red Horse Animation Richard Landry; prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1111)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints, undated (Box 27, Folder 1112)
    - The Red Horse Animation photocopies, undated (Box 27, Folder 1113)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints; "Comic", undated (Box 27, Folder 1114)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints; "Comic" 2, undated (Box 27, Folder 1115)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints; "Comic" 3, undated (Box 27, Folder 1116)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints; "Comic" 4, undated (Box 27, Folder 1117)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints; "Comic" 5, undated (Box 27, Folder 1118)
    - The Red Horse Animation prints; "Comic" 6, undated (Box 27, Folder 1119)
    - The Red Horse Animation contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 1120)
    - The Red Horse Animation Benjamin Blackwell; contact sheets, undated (Box 27, Folder 1121)
    - The Red Horse Animation Richard Landry; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 1122)
    - The Red Horse Animation Amnon Ben Nomis; negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1123)
    - The Red Horse Animation Tom Berthiaume; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1124)
    - The Red Horse Animation Roberta Neiman; contact sheets, negatives, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 1125)
    - The Red Horse Animation Babette Mangolte; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1126)
    - The Red Horse Animation misc. prints photographers include: Babette Mangolte, Richard Landry, Peter Moore, undated (Box 137)
    - Reel to Real Dona Ann McAdams; prints; rehearsal, undated (Box 28, Folder 1127)
    - Reel to Real Paula Court; prints, contact sheets, negatives; April, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1128)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Peter Moore; contact sheets; April 23, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1129)
    - The Saint and the Football Players print, contact sheet; Pratt; Feb 7, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1130)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Peter Moore; contact sheets; Feb 7, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1131)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Tina Girouard; prints, contact sheets, undated (Box 28, Folder 1132)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Tina Girouard; negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1133)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Bob van Dantzig; contact sheets, undated (Box 28, Folder 1134)
    - The Saint and the Football Players prints ("original"), undated (Box 28, Folder 1135)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation prints; work in progress; Cooper Gallery, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1136)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Ken Kobland; contact sheet, undated (Box 28, Folder 1137)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Ken Kobland; print; "Rose in sweatsuit", 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1138)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Ken Kobland; print; "Rose," Terry O'Reilly, Bill Raymond, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1139)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Robin Thomas; print, undated (Box 28, Folder 1140)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation David Stark; print; Oct 17, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1141)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Johan Elbers; prints, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1142)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation L.B. Dallas; prints, contact sheets, undated (Box 28, Folder 1143)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Nathaniel Tileston; contact sheet; Soho; March, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1144)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Donna Gray; contact sheets, undated (Box 28, Folder 1145)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various; negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1146)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema Ilaria Freccia; prints, undated (Box 28, Folder 1147)
    - Southern Exposure Wolfgang Staehle; prints, undated (Box 28, Folder 1148)
    - Southern Exposure Ken Kobland; print; The Performing Garage, undated (Box 28, Folder 1149)
    - Southern Exposure Ken Kobland, Wolfgang Staehle; negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1150)
    - Starcock Massimo Agus; print, contact sheet, undated (Box 28, Folder 1151)
    - Starcock David Dessel; print, undated (Box 28, Folder 1152)
    - Sueños Lisa Stein; contact sheets, undated (Box 28, Folder 1153)
    - Sueños Lisa Stein; prints; American Repertory Theatre, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1154)
    - Sueños Peter Schweizer; contact sheets, negatives for reprint; American Repertory Theatre, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1155)
    - Sueños Peter Schweizer; prints; American Repertory Theatre, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1156)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; prints; Saez and Milián; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1157)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; prints; Feb, undated (Box 28, Folder 1158)
    - Sueños Peter Schweizer; print; Milián and Smith; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1159)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; print; chorus; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1160)
    - Sueños Carol Rosegg; contact sheets; Triplex Theatre; Feb, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1161)
    - Sueños Jonathan Atkin; contact sheets, negative; "New York Times"; March, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1162)
    - Through the Leaves Nancy Campbell; prints; Interart Theater, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1163a)
    - Through the Leaves Donna Gray; print, contact negatives, [1984] (Box 29, Folder 1163b)
    - Through the Leaves Gerry Goodstein; print, [1984] (Box 29, Folder 1164)
    - Through the Leaves Joseph Schuyler; prints, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1165)
    - Through the Leaves prints, [1984] (Box 29, Folder 1166)
    - Through the Leaves Nancy Campbell, Joseph Schuyler; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 1167)
    - Vanishing Pictures Craig Massey, Stephanie Rudolph, undated (Box 29, Folder 1168)
    - Worstward Ho Robin Holland; contact sheets, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1169)
    - Worstward Ho JoAnn Baker; contact sheets, negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 1170)
    - Worstward Ho Dona Ann McAdams; prints, negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 1171)
    - Worstward Ho prints (snapshots), undated (Box 29, Folder 1172)
    - Worstward Ho negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 1173)
    - Wrong Guys Craig Massey; prints, contact sheets, undated (Box 29, Folder 1174)
    - Wrong Guys Craig Massey; prints, negatives, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1175)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; prints, negatives, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1176)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; prints, negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 1177)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; print, negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 1178)
    - Wrong Guys Carol Rosegg; contact sheets, undated (Box 29, Folder 1179)
    - Wrong Guys Nancy Campbell; print, negative, contact sheets, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1180)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; print, contact sheet, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1181)
    - Wrong Guys contact sheet, undated (Box 29, Folder 1182)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity still, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1183)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1184)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1185)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1186)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1187)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1188)
    - Wrong Guys Ilaria Freccia; publicity stills, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1189)
    - Wrong Guys publicity still, [1981] (Box 29, Folder 1190)
  - Subseries B: Company and miscellaneous photographs
    Mabou Mines company photographs, photos of anniversary events, cast members' head shots, and documentary photographs of Mabou Mines-affiliated productions, photo and slide (see Series V) inventory. All major Mabou Mines members (Akalaitis, Breuer, Maleczech, Neumann, Raymond, Warrilow, etc.) are represented by head shots.
    - Company photos Amnon Ben Nomis; prints, contact sheets, negatives; group shot, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1191)
    - Company photos Nancy Campbell; print, contact sheets; group shot, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1192)
    - Company photos Paula Court; prints, negatives, contact sheets; [includes photos of Joseph Papp, David Byrne, et al.]; 15th Anniversary Benefit, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1193)
    - Company photos Joseph Schuyler; contact sheet; The First 20 Years, Grey Art Gallery, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1194)
    - Head shots print; Ellen McElduff, undated (Box 30, Folder 1195)
    - Head shots print, negative; JoAnne Akalaitis, undated (Box 30, Folder 1196)
    - Head shots prints, contact sheets; Bill Raymond, undated (Box 30, Folder 1197)
    - Head shots print; Terry O'Reilly, undated (Box 30, Folder 1198)
    - Head shots passport photos; Honora Fergusson, Sabrina Hamilton, undated (Box 30, Folder 1199)
    - Head shots print, passport photo; Frederick Neumann, undated (Box 30, Folder 1200)
    - Head shots prints, negative; Lee Breuer, undated (Box 30, Folder 1201)
    - Head shots print, negative; Lee Breuer, undated (Box 30, Folder 1202)
    - Head shots Amnon Ben Nomis; print, negative; Lee Breuer, undated (Box 30, Folder 1203)
    - Head shots prints; Ruth Maleczech, two poses, undated (Box 30, Folder 1204)
    - Head shots Craig Massey; print, negative; David Warrilow, undated (Box 30, Folder 1205)
    - Head shots prints; Lear, George Street cast, undated (Box 30, Folder 1206)
    - Head shots Roger Pic, Editions de Minuit; prints; Samuel Beckett, undated (Box 30, Folder 1207)
    - Head shots print; Drew Minter, undated (Box 30, Folder 1208)
    - Head shots print; Jeffrey Morreau, undated (Box 30, Folder 1209)
    - Head shots photocopy; Ron Vawter and Greg Mehrten, undated (Box 30, Folder 1210)
    - Head shots print; unidentified actor, undated (Box 30, Folder 1211)
    - Miscellaneous photos Ricky McKay; prints; Re-Cher-Chez, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1212)
    - Miscellaneous photos Craig Massey; print, negative; David Warrilow, "A Piece of Monologue", undated (Box 30, Folder 1213)
    - Miscellaneous photos prints; "Waiting for Godot"; Kent State Univeristy, undated (Box 30, Folder 1214)
    - Miscellaneous photos prints; Kent State Univeristy, Fine and Performing Arts Center, undated (Box 30, Folder 1215)
    - Miscellaneous photos Ann W. Arlen; contact sheets, letter; Lee and Bill workshop, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1216)
    - Miscellaneous photos Martha Swope; print; "Red and Blue," dir. JoAnne Akalaitis, undated (Box 30, Folder 1217)
    - Miscellaneous photos unidentified snapshots, undated (Box 30, Folder 1218)
    - Miscellaneous photos unidentified personal negatives, undated (Box 137)
    - Inventory photo and press inventory as of August 1984 (Box 30, Folder 1219)
    - Inventory photo and slide inventory, November 10, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 1220)
- Series V: Slides
  Series V comprises several hundred slides, some documentary, some actual production elements. The slides were originally housed in either plastic sleeves grouped in three-ring binders, or plastic or cardboard slide boxes. The original labeling on these housings was faithfully transcribed.
  - Subseries A: Documentary slides
    Slides of documentary photographs of Mabou Mines productions.
    - The B. Beaver Animation, July 1973 (Box 32, Folder 1225)
    - The Bribe, undated (Box 32, Folder 1226)
    - Cold Harbor photographer: Georgina Bedrosian; San Francisco tour photos, 1987, 1987, undated (Box 32, Folder 1227)
    - Dead End Kids, undated (Box 32, Folder 1228)
    - Dressed Like an Egg etc. photographer: Ken Kobland, June 1977, 1977, undated (Box 32, Folder 1229)
    - Flow My Tears, the Policeman Said photographers include: Anne E. Militello; Martha Swope Associates/Carol Rosegg; Jeff Thiebauth, undated (Box 32, Folder 1230)
    - Hajj, undated (Box 32, Folder 1231)
    - Help Wanted, undated (Box 32, Folder 1232)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine photographers include: Andre Grossmann, May 1984; others June 1984-Nov 1985, 1984-5 (Box 32, Folder 1233)
    - It's a Man's World photographer: George Mott; New York, NY, June, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1234)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice photographers include: Amnon B. Nomis, May 1986, 1979, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1235)
    - Pretty Boy photographer: Nancy Campbell, March 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1236)
    - The Red Horse Animation some Jan 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1237)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation photographers include: Ken Kobland, March 1978; Robin Thomas (Box 32, Folder 1238)
    - The Saint and the Football Players July 1973 (Box 32, Folder 1239)
    - Sueños, undated (Box 32, Folder 1240)
    - Through the Leaves Interart Theatre, March-May 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1241)
    - Through the Leaves April 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1242)
    - Through the Leaves photographer: Joseph Schuyler, Sept 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1243)
    - Vanishing Pictures photographer: Ilaria Freccia, [1980] (Box 32, Folder 1244)
    - Worstward Ho photographer: JoAnn Baker, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1245)
    - ...The First 20 Years photographer: Joseph Schuyler; Grey Art Gallery, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1246)
  - Subseries B: Production slides
    Slides used as production elements in various Mabou Mines productions.
    - Cold Harbor, undated (Box 33, Folder 1247)
    - Cold Harbor spare slides, rehearsal 1, undated (Box 33, Folder 1248)
    - Cold Harbor spare slides, rehearsal 2, undated (Box 33, Folder 1249)
    - Cold Harbor spare slides, rehearsal 3, undated (Box 33, Folder 1250)
    - Dead End Kids, undated (Box 33, Folder 1251)
    - Flow My Tears, the Policeman Said, undated (Box 33, Folder 1252)
    - It's a Man's World, undated (Box 33, Folder 1253)
    - Mercier and Camier "ST RUTH LEFT", undated (Box 33, Folder 1254)
    - Mercier and Camier "TRAIN RIGHT BOTTOM"; Bill Longcore photos, undated (Box 33, Folder 1255)
    - Mercier and Camier "TRAIN RIGHT TOP", undated (Box 33, Folder 1256)
    - Mercier and Camier "TRAIN LEFT BOTTOM", undated (Box 33, Folder 1257)
    - Mercier and Camier David Warrilow, undated (Box 33, Folder 1258)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice beach scene, undated (Box 33, Folder 1259)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation dog pictures, undated (Box 33, Folder 1260)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation "damaged or need cleaning", undated (Box 33, Folder 1261)
    - Starcock, undated (Box 33, Folder 1262)
    - Sueños A-I: dictator's maps; J-M1: research slides, undated (Box 33, Folder 1263)
    - miscellaneous unidentified production slides, undated (Box 33, Folder 1264)
- Series VI: Scripts
  Scripts, drafts, notes, film treatments, and screenplays representing a majority of Mabou Mines' productions, and some Mabou Mines-affiliated productions. Of particular interest are the many drafts and early versions of Lee Breuer's works, scripts notated by Ruth Maleczech, and a monologue written by Samuel Beckett for David Warrilow.
  Boxes stored offsite: Box 34 - Barcode: 31142042235948 Box 35 - Barcode: 31142042235955 Box 36 - Barcode: 31142042235963 Box 136 - Barcode: 31142042236219
  - The B. Beaver Animation Lee Breuer, undated (Box 34, Folder 1265)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042235948
  - The B. Beaver Animation Lee Breuer in "Big Deal," 4 (Fall 1976) (Box 34, Folder 1266)
  - The B. Beaver Animation Lee Breuer in "Animations: A Trilogy for Mabou Mines" (New York: Performing Arts Journal Publications), 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1267)
  - The Bribe Terry O'Reilly radio script, undated (Box 34, Folder 1268)
  - Cacodemon King Bernard Chartreux, undated (Box 34, Folder 1269)
  - Cascando Samuel Beckett (New York: Grove Press, Inc.), [1968] (Box 34, Folder 1270)
  - C.E.O. Stig Larsson, trans. Joe Martin, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 1271)